[
    {"question": "have a soft spot for sth/sb", "answer": "〜に弱い、どうしても好き"},
    {"question": "for the foreseeable future", "answer": "しばらくは"},
    {"question": "back-seat driver", "answer": "とやかく言う人"},
    {"question": "hard on sb", "answer": "〜に厳しい、きつく当たる"},
    {"question": "pull at sb's heartstrings", "answer": "〜を感動させる"},
    {"question": "foot the bill", "answer": "残りを支払う；全額支払う"},
    {"question": "on top of the world", "answer": "最高の気分の、とても幸せな"},
    {"question": "get back to (the) basic", "answer": "基本に戻る"},
    {"question": "sit on sth", "answer": "〜を遅らせる"},
    {"question": "force the issue", "answer": "決着をつける、はっきりさせる"},
    {"question": "view sth in a certain light", "answer": "〜に対してある見方をする"},
    {"question": "by and large", "answer": "全体的には、一般的には"},
    {"question": "be killing sb", "answer": "しんどい、本当無理である"},
    {"question": "live with sth", "answer": "〜を受け入れる、耐える"},
    {"question": "go off track", "answer": "（話題や予定から）それる、ズレる"},
    {"question": "land on one's feet", "answer": "（困難や窮地を）乗り越える、立ち直る"},
    {"question": "fingers crossed", "answer": "（幸運や成功を）祈る"},
    {"question": "done deal", "answer": "既に決まったこと、終わった話"},
    {"question": "that ship has sailed", "answer": "時すでに遅し、もう遅い"},
    {"question": "checks and balances", "answer": "抑制と均衡"},

    {"question": "lighten the mood", "answer": "雰囲気をよくする、明るくする"},
    {"question": "something along those lines", "answer": "それ系のもの、そんな感じのこと"},
    {"question": "do sth for the sake of doing sth", "answer": "〜自体が目的化している"},
    {"question": "on point", "answer": "キマっている、カッコいい"},
    {"question": "have a word with sb", "answer": "〜と少し話す"},
    {"question": "insurance policy", "answer": "万が一の保険"},
    {"question": "hot-headed", "answer": "短期な"},
    {"question": "better safe than sorry", "answer": "念のため、備えあれば憂いなし"},
    {"question": "put all one's eggs in one basket", "answer": "ひとつに全てを賭ける、つぎ込む"},
    {"question": "batch sth", "answer": "〜をまとめてする"},
    {"question": "keep things moving", "answer": "（物事を）進め続ける、活動を維持する"},
    {"question": "hit a roadblock", "answer": "困難にぶつかる"},
    {"question": "that's a first", "answer": "めずらしい、初めてだよ"},
    {"question": "fed up", "answer": "うんざりした"},
    {"question": "see eye to eye", "answer": "意見が合う"},
    {"question": "stick it out", "answer": "最後まで頑張る、耐える"},
    {"question": "in the grand scheme of things", "answer": "全体的に見れば"},
    {"question": "in and of itself", "answer": "これだけで、それだけで"},
    {"question": "get sth out the door", "answer": "〜を終わらせる、完成させる"},
    {"question": "bank on sth/sb", "answer": "〜をあてにする、期待する"},

    {"question": "blanket term", "answer": "総称"},
    {"question": "have no filter", "answer": "（考えずに）ズバズバ言う"},
    {"question": "set the bar high", "answer": "ハードルを上げる、基準を高くする"},
    {"question": "get to the bottom of sth", "answer": "〜の原因を突き止める"},
    {"question": "can't be helped", "answer": "仕方ない、どうしようもない"},
    {"question": "back in the day", "answer": "昔は"},
    {"question": "going nowhere", "answer": "進展がない、行き詰まっている"},
    {"question": "too little, too late", "answer": "今更遅い、時すでに遅し"},
    {"question": "all hands on desk", "answer": "みんなで力を合わせた"},
    {"question": "hang sb out to dry", "answer": "〜を危険な状態にさらす；見捨てる"},
    {"question": "err on the side of caution", "answer": "慎重になる"},
    {"question": "between a rock and a hard place", "answer": "板挟みになって"},
    {"question": "keep one's head above the water", "answer": "ギリギリの状態でいる"},
    {"question": "shaky", "answer": "たどたどしい、不安定な"},
    {"question": "drop a bombshell", "answer": "衝撃的な発言をする"},
    {"question": "for the record", "answer": "（念のために）言っておくけど"},
    {"question": "stockpile sth", "answer": "〜を貯める"},
    {"question": "judge a book by its color", "answer": "見た目で判断する"},
    {"question": "on a positive note", "answer": "ポジティブに考えれば"},
    {"question": "take off", "answer": "（場所を）出る；うまくいく"},

    {"question": "draw the short straw", "answer": "（くじ）運が悪い"},
    {"question": "take it out on sb", "answer": "〜に八つ当たりする"},
    {"question": "go through sth with a fine-tooth comb", "answer": ""},
    {"question": "have a free rein", "answer": "〜を細かくチョックする"},
    {"question": "hold off on sth", "answer": "〜を遠慮する、ちょっと待つ"},
    {"question": "in the dark", "answer": "分からない状態で"},
    {"question": "unpack sth", "answer": "〜を整理する、説明する"},
    {"question": "hold one's horses", "answer": "（急がず）ちょっと待つ"},
    {"question": "get it over with", "answer": "さっさと（終わらせる）"},
    {"question": "sold on sth", "answer": "〜にしっくりきた、信じた"},
    {"question": "choke", "answer": "（大事な場面で）プレッシャーに負ける"},
    {"question": "formo", "answer": "取り残される恐怖"},
    {"question": "have a change of heart", "answer": "気が変わる、気持ちが変化する"},
    {"question": "suck up to sb", "answer": "〜にごまをする、媚びる"},
    {"question": "silver bullet", "answer": "特効薬、簡単な解決法"},
    {"question": "bookworm", "answer": "本好き"},
    {"question": "go for broke", "answer": "全力を尽くす"},
    {"question": "strong suit", "answer": "強み、得意分野"},
    {"question": "pick sb's brain", "answer": "〜の知識を借りる"},
    {"question": "textbook", "answer": "教科書通りの、完璧な"},

    {"question": "to each their own", "answer": "人それぞれ好みが違う"},
    {"question": "save face", "answer": "メンツを保つ"},
    {"question": "get behind sth", "answer": "〜をサポートする"},
    {"question": "as it stands", "answer": "現状では"},
    {"question": "broaden one's horizons", "answer": "視野を広げる"},
    {"question": "can't help oneself", "answer": "自分を抑えることができない"},
    {"question": "over the moon", "answer": "大喜びして、最高に幸せな"},
    {"question": "remind me again", "answer": "もう一回教える、思い出させる"},
    {"question": "stumble one's way through sth", "answer": "〜で詰まる、つまずく"},
    {"question": "panicky", "answer": "テンパった、パニクった；不安な"},
    {"question": "below the belt", "answer": "（行為や発言が）卑怯な、汚い"},
    {"question": "one-in-a-million", "answer": "特別な存在の；（可能性が）かなり低い"},
    {"question": "an experience", "answer": "いい経験"},
    {"question": "kill two birds with one stone", "answer": "一石二鳥である"},
    {"question": "pull the plug", "answer": "打ち切る、キャンセルする"},
    {"question": "water under the bridge", "answer": "過ぎたこと、終わったこと"},
    {"question": "top dog", "answer": "最重要人物"},
    {"question": "no news is good news", "answer": "何も知らせがないのは良いことだ"},
    {"question": "get looks from people", "answer": "人にじろじろ見られる"},
    {"question": "slam dunk", "answer": "間違いないもの、確実なこと"}
]